SKILLS

Unreal Bluprint Unreal 4 & 5 Game Design Level Design

LANGUAGES

Portuguese Mother language

English - Proficient/C1 Reading Writing Conversation

Gabriel Lima de Jesus

ABOUT ME

I'm Gabriel Lima de Jesus, a programmer and game designer. I've been creating games since 2019 and currently pursuing a degree in Information Systems at the Federal Institute of Bahia. As part of my academic journey, I contributed as a game designer and programmer to the game 'Aventuras Falciforme' working on Godot. Between 2022 and 2023, I worked at Chave-Mestra, where I started to work as a Game Designer. During this time, I specialized in developing escape games and puzzles for custom projects. In the same year, I showcased my work with GDH Studio on Itch.io through game jams, and in 2023, we released our debut game MONOTONIA: FIRST CONCTACT on the Steam.

EXPERIENCE

Game Designer

Nov 2022 - ongoing

Dedicated professional in game creation, documentation, and balancing, serving as both a Game Designer and Game Developer. Specialized in implementing mechanics and user interfaces using Blueprint

Game Designer

Chave-Mestra Gamificação Gramado, Rio Grande do Sul, Brasil July 2022 - Jan 2024

Game Designer / Game Developer (Godot 3)

July2021 - December 2021

IFBA - Instituto Federal da Bahia

Member of the development and testing team with Godot of Anemia Falciforme game, a serious game aimed at helping children better understand how to cope with Sickle Cell Anemia

EDUCATION

IFBA - Instituto Federal da Bahia Bachelor's degree in Information Systems

2018 - Present

COURSES

IEF SET English Certificate 71/100 (C2 Proficient)

<u>Unreal Engine Blueprint Game Developer</u>

CONTACT

Email: gabriel.lima.contact97@gmail.com

Telefone: (75)992184033